# **Lorenzo Javier Colodro**

# **Full Stack Developer**

🕿 javiercolodro@gmail.com 📞 +54 9358 4392425 👂 Córdoba -Argentina 🞧 Github 📅 Linked In 🔗 Portfolio

### **ABOUT ME**

My experience in aviation has been a significant part of my personal and professional growth for 5 years. In this new stage in programming, I am excited to apply the skills I acquired through an intensive JavaScript Bootcamp. My challenge is to provide valuable contributions to any project I am involved in and meet the needs of the company.

I aim to transition my career and aspirations into the technology sector, combining my programming knowledge with my passion for delivering an excellent customer service.

### **PROJECTS**

# FullStack Developer - Comunidad Perros&Gatos APP

09/2024 - 11/2024

- Developed an application allowing users to register and apply for pet adoptions, with a focus on connecting potential adopters to pets in shelters.
- International Collaborative Project in No Country Organization: 5 weeks of development.

Frontend: React Vite, React-Router-Dom, MaterialUi, CSS, Js-cookie.

Backend: Node.js, TypeScript, Prisma, Google Oauth, Express-session, Passport, Cloudinary, Node Mailer, Multer, Docker, PostgreSQL Render Database, Table Plus, Swagger.

## **FullStack Developer - My Favourites Videos APP**

08/2024 - 10/2024

- Developed a Video Gallery application with both backend and frontend components, enabling users to store their favourite videos and manage personal video preferences.
- Personal Project: 2 months of development.

Frontend: React Vite, TypeScript, Redux, Tailwind CSS, Axios, React-Router-Dom, Toastify, Lite-youtube, Heroicons. Backend Node.js, TypeScript, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Sequelize-Cli, Bcryptjs, Node Mailer, Jsonwebtoken.

#### FullStack Developer - To Do App

05/2024 - 09/2024

- Developed a To Do App that enables users to register, log in, and manage their tasks by adding, updating, and deleting chores.
- Personal Project: 5 months of development.

Frontend: React Vite, React-Router-Dom, Tailwind, Redux, Cypress, React Spinners, Sooner,

Backend: Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Sequelize-Cli, Joi, Node Mailer, Bcryptjs, Jest, Supertest, Swagger.

Agile Methodologies: Experience with Scrum, using tools like Trello for task management, and participating in daily standups to review progress, address challenges, and align daily goals.

Explore additional projects &

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML | CSS | SASS | JAVASCRIPT | REACT | REACT ROUTER DOM | SEQUELIZE | PRISMA | NODEJS | TYPESCRIPT | POSTGRESQL | REDUX | BOOTSTRAP | GITHUB | POSTMAN | TAILWIND | JEST | SUPERTEST | CYPRESS | CLOUDINARY | NODEMAILER | RESEND | DOCKER | TABLE PLUS | SWAGGER | TOASTIFY | RENDER | JOI | SOONER | JSONWEBTOKEN | BCRIPTJS

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Technical Support in Call Center**

11/2021 – 12/2022

- Managing and responding to 30-40 phone calls, chats, and emails daily to ensure optimal customer assistance.
- Providing support and assistance to customers across 34 states in the United States and Central America.

10/2014 - 01/2021 **Cabin Crew** 

- I was responsible for the safety and excellent service to customers on 23 domestic flights and 22 international destinations.
- I had the opportunity to supervise 10 regional flights for junior crew members and achieve improved performance.

## **EDUCATION**

## **JavaScript Bootcamp on Plataforma 5**

09/2023

- +1000 hours of coding
- 9 AM to 7 PM schedule
- 7 months intensive
- Pair-programming activities
- Agile methodologies: Scrum, Planning, Daily Stand-up, Review, Demo, and Trello.

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish Native
- English C1